♪♪♪
♪ AS I WALK THROUGH ♪
♪ THIS WICKED WORLD ♪
♪ SEARCHIN' FOR LIGHT IN
THE DARKNESS OF INSANITY ♪
♪ I ASK MYSELF ♪
♪ IS ALL HOPE LOST ♪
♪ IS THERE ONLY PAIN
AND HATRED, AND MISERY ♪
♪ AND EACH TIME I FEEL
LIKE THIS INSIDE ♪
♪ THERE'S ONE THING
I WANNA KNOW ♪
♪ WHAT'S SO FUNNY 'BOUT PEACE,
LOVE AND UNDERSTANDING ♪
♪ OH ♪
♪ WHAT'S SO FUNNY 'BOUT PEACE,
LOVE AND UNDERSTANDING ♪
♪ AND AS I WALKED ON ♪
♪ THROUGH TROUBLED TIMES ♪
♪ MY SPIRIT GETS SO
DOWNHEARTED SOMETIMES ♪
♪ SO WHERE ARE THE STRONG ♪
♪ AND WHO ARE THE TRUSTED ♪
♪ AND WHERE IS THE HARMONY ♪
♪ SWEET HARMONY ♪
♪ 'CAUSE EACH TIME I
FEEL IT SLIPPIN' AWAY ♪
♪ JUST MAKES ME WANNA CRY ♪
♪ WHAT'S SO FUNNY 'BOUT PEACE,
LOVE AND UNDERSTANDING ♪
♪ OH ♪
♪ WHAT'S SO FUNNY 'BOUT PEACE,
LOVE AND UNDERSTANDING ♪
♪♪♪
♪ SO WHERE ARE THE STRONG ♪
♪ AND WHO ARE THE TRUSTED ♪
♪ AND WHERE IS THE HARMONY ♪
♪ SWEET HARMONY ♪
♪ 'CAUSE EACH TIME I
FEEL IT SLIPPIN' AWAY ♪
♪ JUST MAKES ME WANNA CRY ♪
♪ WHAT'S SO FUNNY 'BOUT PEACE,
LOVE AND UNDERSTANDING ♪
♪ OH ♪
♪ WHAT'S SO FUNNY 'BOUT PEACE,
LOVE AND UNDERSTANDING ♪
♪ OH ♪
♪ WHAT'S SO FUN ABOUT PEACE,
LOVE AND UNDERSTANDING ♪